<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aoife Hayes</title>
    <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aoife Hayes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Aoife Hayes 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exhibition Catalogue</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/catalogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/catalogue/</guid>
      <description>Melanie McGrath
What Once Was (2022)
Ink on paper
Benjamin Walsh
Where Can We Rent? (2022)
Film images on paper
Emma Price
Realm (2022) &amp;amp; Untitled works 1, 2 &amp;amp; 3 (2022)
Analog image on bamboo paper
Lily O&amp;rsquo;Shea
a plan of a plan (2022)
Plywood</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Has My Practice Developed</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/develop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/develop/</guid>
      <description>Reflecting on these initial journal entries now, I am confident that I respected the intentions set at the beginning of the academic year. While my core values remain the same, my research interests have undergone a transformation. I believe this shift to be a result of the specific temporal cross contamination of retail work, academia and curatorial practice.
When setting out to co-produce host/ghost, I was primarily concerned with the urban environment, its neglection and how it might be better cared for in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commissioning a plan of a plan</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/commission/</guid>
      <description>a plan of a plan is an unfinished artwork by Lily O’Shea that is based on the structure of a staircase. It is accompanied by a text titled life in a project: a time of no time which explores the relationship between project work and precarity. The research process involved in this work focuses on the pressures surrounding creative pursuit and the issue of affording the time and space to maintain a sustainable art practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curating a plan of a plan</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curating/</guid>
      <description>Detailed here are the practical elements of curating a plan of a plan. Sensitive information such as budget and contract are included in full in the appendices accompanying the introduction to this portfolio.
host/ghost commission budget Lily O’Shea was paid an artist fee for her work. Installation costs were low and the venue cost was split between the three producers occupying St Peter’s.
Contract A letter of agreement was issued to Lily O’Shea on 30th March 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Aoife Hayes is a Cork-based curator from Co. Kerry. Her curatorial practice’s primary research concerns include alternative methodologies of productivity and chronopolitics.
Recent curatorial projects include; host/ghost, co-curated with Glenn Dunlea, St Peter’s Cork; CRUSH, Backwater Artists Group.
Currently completing a Masters of Arts in Arts Management &amp;amp; Creative Producing at University College Cork. Aoife completed her BA Joint Hons in History of Art &amp;amp; French from University College Cork with honours in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Aoife Hayes
aoife.haze@gmail.com
Education
University College Cork, MA in Arts Management &amp;amp; Creative Producing, 2022.
University College Cork, BA Hons History of Art &amp;amp; French, 2017.
Experience
Selection committee at Backwater Artists Group for Ciarán Langford Memorial Bursary and Moving Image Bursary 2022.
PR &amp;amp; Event Production at Rebound Arts Festival, 2022
Voiceover work for Ocras by Eoin Ó Fíannachta at NOISE Moves Youth Dance Festival, 2021. Visual Art &amp;amp; Curatorial Assistant at K-Fest Arts &amp;amp; Music Festival, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a plan of a plan and the curatorial</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curatorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curatorial/</guid>
      <description>Curatorial projects are increasingly understood as ongoing research projects rather than once off events. As such, I wish to outline my intention to carry the framework identified in the process of curating a plan of a plan through to future practice and research.
While host/ghost was specific to Cork and the local context of urban neglect and dereliction, the curatorial here encompasses a wider approach to practice rooted in sustainable and interdependent practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Note on Festival</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/festivalnote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/festivalnote/</guid>
      <description>I am reflecting on the concept of festival – a word that has defined the past year in many ways.
The concept of festival represents an experimental social space and undertaking. The diversity of events presented at Rebound Arts Festival demonstrates playfulness regarding perceptions of what a festival can be and what it can lead to.
Emerging from pandemic-related lockdowns, there was a sense that a celebration like Rebound Arts Festival had been delayed – which made it all the more special as it unfolded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR Department</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/rebound/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/rebound/pr/</guid>
      <description>The primary collective roles of the PR department included the creation of a press pack and press release and liaison with the public, media and critical friends.
PR meetings were held weekly during the 12-week production timeline and more regularly in the lead up to the publication of our press release, press pack and festival launch event.
Press Release and Press Pack The creation of a press release required the identification of Rebound Arts Festival’s unique selling point.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
