<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>host/ghost on Aoife Hayes</title>
    <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/</link>
    <description>Recent content in host/ghost on Aoife Hayes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Aoife Hayes 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exhibition Catalogue</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/catalogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/catalogue/</guid>
      <description>Melanie McGrath
What Once Was (2022)
Ink on paper
Benjamin Walsh
Where Can We Rent? (2022)
Film images on paper
Emma Price
Realm (2022) &amp;amp; Untitled works 1, 2 &amp;amp; 3 (2022)
Analog image on bamboo paper
Lily O&amp;rsquo;Shea
a plan of a plan (2022)
Plywood</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commissioning a plan of a plan</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/commission/</guid>
      <description>a plan of a plan is an unfinished artwork by Lily O’Shea that is based on the structure of a staircase. It is accompanied by a text titled life in a project: a time of no time which explores the relationship between project work and precarity. The research process involved in this work focuses on the pressures surrounding creative pursuit and the issue of affording the time and space to maintain a sustainable art practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curating a plan of a plan</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curating/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curating/</guid>
      <description>Detailed here are the practical elements of curating a plan of a plan. Sensitive information such as budget and contract are included in full in the appendices accompanying the introduction to this portfolio.
host/ghost commission budget Lily O’Shea was paid an artist fee for her work. Installation costs were low and the venue cost was split between the three producers occupying St Peter’s.
Contract A letter of agreement was issued to Lily O’Shea on 30th March 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a plan of a plan and the curatorial</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curatorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/hostghost/curatorial/</guid>
      <description>Curatorial projects are increasingly understood as ongoing research projects rather than once off events. As such, I wish to outline my intention to carry the framework identified in the process of curating a plan of a plan through to future practice and research.
While host/ghost was specific to Cork and the local context of urban neglect and dereliction, the curatorial here encompasses a wider approach to practice rooted in sustainable and interdependent practice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
