<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reflections on Aoife Hayes</title>
    <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reflections on Aoife Hayes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Aoife Hayes 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Has My Practice Developed</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/develop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/develop/</guid>
      <description>Reflecting on these initial journal entries now, I am confident that I respected the intentions set at the beginning of the academic year. While my core values remain the same, my research interests have undergone a transformation. I believe this shift to be a result of the specific temporal cross contamination of retail work, academia and curatorial practice.
When setting out to co-produce host/ghost, I was primarily concerned with the urban environment, its neglection and how it might be better cared for in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Note on Festival</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/festivalnote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/festivalnote/</guid>
      <description>I am reflecting on the concept of festival – a word that has defined the past year in many ways.
The concept of festival represents an experimental social space and undertaking. The diversity of events presented at Rebound Arts Festival demonstrates playfulness regarding perceptions of what a festival can be and what it can lead to.
Emerging from pandemic-related lockdowns, there was a sense that a celebration like Rebound Arts Festival had been delayed – which made it all the more special as it unfolded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aoifehayes-ma-amcp.github.io/reflections/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
